Hello? This is Kagami, from Kunahama High.
Yes. We've got more members now,
so if possible, we'd like the help
of Takafuji, the powerhouse school.
If you would be so kind,
we'd love to hold a joint
training camp with you.
Lend me your ear, everyone.
Takafuji Academy FC Team Training Area
Maintaining proper posture
is key to field flying.
Focus on the task at hand, and get to work.
Yes!
You're flailing your arms, Kurashina-san.
Right!
I have to keep my arms steady.
Now your legs are flailing.
Legs steady!
Picture yourself floating
in a pool. Relax your body.
Wow, she's gotten a lot better
at flying since her first day.
Misaki-senpai really is amazing.
Stabilize your upper body!
Next up, Ichinose Rika.
Got it.
H-Hey...
Second field-flying group setting off!
Episode Three:
"I Just Got a Little Fired Up"
What? Masaya saw you changing twice?
What a creep! He deserves a public execution!
Anyway, this training
camp's got me thinking.
Is practice at Takafuji always this brutal?
I can't keep up at all.
I'm no good at all.
But that's what makes Takafuji a powerhouse.
Makes me glad I go to Kunahama.
And you're a starter here?
You're incredible, Ichinose-san.
Oh, no. I have a long way to go.
Speaking of Takafuji, your captain...
Shindou-san, was it?
Haven't seen him around.
He's supposed to return from the
invitational training camp for students soon.
Invitational? He must be good, then?
"Good"? He's the reigning national champion.
Really?
That's news to me!
Apparently he's even had scouts from
Europe's pro leagues come to watch him.
A future professional, huh?
No wonder they make you work
your tails off in practice.
And Satouin-san was like
a drill sergeant, too.
Eh?
Pardon my tardiness.
Speak of the devil.
I, Satouin Reiko,
have arrived to wash the backs
of you fine ladies from Kunahama.
Not again!
She had her way with you yesterday,
and she's still not done?
Let us begin,
Tobisawa-san.
Me?!
No way...
Sorry for your loss.
Where are you going?!
H-Hey, wait!
Are you ready?
Come on, sit still!
Stop it!
Hang in there, Senpai!
I'll watch your valiant efforts to the end!
N-No, don't!
T-Time out! Pawse!
Running simulations of the practice matches?
That's right. Why do you ask?
I'm the captain of the
Takafuji Academy FC Team,
Shindou Kazunari.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hinata Masaya, from Kunahama High.
Nice to meet you, too.
I wasn't planning to go to the
invitational training camp,
but they insisted I drop by.
How's practice?
Is it helping the Kunahama players at all?
Yeah. Thanks to you, we've improved a lot.
But...
But?
Takafuji's honestly way out of our league.
I don't see this camp
benefiting you in any way.
So why did you agree?
Well, partly because it was
Kagami-sensei's request.
And partly because I idolized
a certain player in the past.
I picked up FC because
I wanted to be like him,
but he disappeared from the spotlight.
Beating him in a match was my dream.
That's why I agreed to this training camp.
Hinata-kun,
could you play against me?
I don't play FC anymore,
so I can't face you. Sorry.
If you quit, then what made you come back?
The girl who supposedly used an air kick turn
to score against our vice captain?
Well...
I guess I'll see for myself tomorrow.
Eat up, my lovelies.
You can't develop physical
strength unless you eat well.
Here you go!
Hey, Bro, that's your fifth bowl!
Thanks for the food.
Done already, Arisaka-san?
I don't have much of an appetite.
And you sure have a lot of meat
on your plate, Ichinose-san.
Well, I love meat.
You're stuffing your face,
too, Kurashina-senpai!
I need to build up my strength!
Man, if only I'd brought
my nukazuke pickles.
How could I furget?
That's Misaki-senpai for you.
Marches to the beat of her own drum.
Attention, everybody.
Tomorrow's the last day of camp.
We'll be holding practice
matches between Takafuji teams,
and between Takafuji and
Kunahama representatives.
Matches at last!
I can't wait!
Let's do our best.
But I'm still at such a low level.
I expect all of us to give it our all.
Right!
You're eating too much, Bro.
There's room for more!
Ta-dah!
I feasted my eyes on it
in the locker room earlier,
but you really do look
awesome, Misaki-senpai!
You're so sexy, I want to jump—
That looks great on you, Tobisawa-san.
It's my junior high suit.
I brought it along in
case there were matches.
It's better than a swimsuit,
but this is still pretty revealing.
Quit ogling her with such
lecherous eyes, Hinata-senpai.
Anyway, look at this.
Kunahama vs Takafuji
Practices Matches Draw
Match 1:
Kurashina Asuka vs. Ichinose Rika
Match 2:
Arisaka Mashiro vs. Satouin Reiko
Match 3:
Tobisawa Misaki vs. Shindou Kazunari
It's the draw for the practice matches.
Show me!
The Takafuji reps are all starters!
Not to mention Shindou-san's playing, too!
We're gonna get crushed!
Huh? I don't see the captain's name on here.
"F-Forgive me!"
"Not even my abs could
subdue this stomachache!"
...he said.
Wait, why am I taking on Shindou-san?
They asked for Kunahama's
current best player.
Hey.
Shindou-san.
Let's have some good games today.
Oh, so this is him.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
So you're not the one facing me, huh?
I heard you played well
against our vice captain.
N-Not at all. I only scored one point.
Considering you'd never played FC before,
scoring a point against her
is an amazing feat by itself.
Your second's instructions
must have been on point.
Let's have a good game.
Later.
I'm the one you're playing, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's go.
Let's have a good game.
I-I'll do my best!
You're up against a speeder.
Take a shortcut and head her off.
Okay!
Just keep your eyes fixed on your opponent.
I'll tell you what to do.
Got it!
On your marks...
Set!
Take a shortcut, Kurashina-san!
R-Right!
Point to Ichinose!
That's one point down!
What was that Ichinose-san just did?
That's called a low yo-yo.
By descending, you take advantage
of Earth's gravity to accelerate,
and then use that acceleration
to gain altitude.
It's a move that increases flight speed.
I'll ambush her.
Kurashina-san, follow her.
Sure!
Attacking!
Oh, no, you're not.
Whoa! She's fast!
You don't have time to be impressed!
R-Right!
Wow, this is so exciting!
Don't chase after her!
Take a shortcut to the third line!
Okay!
The second point...
...is mine!
Point to Ichinose! 2-0!
Hey, she's using a low yo-yo again!
Which means she'll come back up, right?
Exactly. But we're gonna
stop her before she does.
Fly 45 degrees downwards!
Okay!
That's the way.
Catch me if you can!
Oh, you can't!
Smart move.
What was?
She cut off her descent and
suddenly gained elevation.
She sacrificed the speed she was building up.
She's playing that way because she
knows her opponent's a beginner.
She's good, that Ichinose-san.
Kurashina-san.
Forget about that and move on.
I think I'm starting to get it.
What do you mean?
Call it...
intuition.
Point to Ichinose.
She's coming right at her this time!
I'll go after her!
And that zigzag move just now?
Scissors.
You move left and right
to confuse your opponent.
But while she did get confused,
she's still barely keeping up.
Yeah.
Kurashina-san's movements have clearly
gotten better since the start of the match.
She's the type that thrives
on competition, huh?
Is your tummy okay, Bro?!
Don't worry about it.
4-0!
Keep your eyes on Ichinose-san and
figure out how she's gonna move.
Understood.
I'll go after her.
Wait...
It's a high yo-yo.
Another point is mine!
She's going to touch her back!
A-An air kick turn?!
I did it!
Point to Kurashina!
All right!
This match is over!
In the end, I could only
score one point again.
I'm no good at all.
Nah.
You've gotten a lot better,
and not just at the basics.
I couldn't believe my eyes.
Don't you agree, Misaki?
Yeah. You're improving at an explosive speed.
Wait!
W-Wait, I-I'm up next.
Shall we go, Arisaka-san?
I'll work you over nice and good.
No!
This match is over!
Satouin Reiko of Takafuji Academy wins 20-0.
You're too harsh, Drill Sergeant.
Excuse me?
Well, uh, good game.
Please make sure you put up
a better fight next time.
'Kay...
Too bad, Hinata-kun. Looks like
you're going to lose all three.
Captain.
Shindou—
Hey, we don't know for sure that
I'm gonna lose the last match.
Perhaps.
Well, I hope it's a good
learning experience for you.
Them's fighting words, buddy.
Don't lose your head, Misaki.
It's all good.
I just got a little fired up.
The next matchup:
Shindou Kazunari of Takafuji Academy
versus Tobisawa Misaki of Kunahama High.
Let's have a good game.
Yes, let's.
Shindou-san's an all-rounder.
You're a fighter, so you
have a speed disadvantage.
Yeah. I'll start by taking a shortcut.
That's right.
On your marks...
Set!
Step on it, Misaki!
What's wrong?
Shindou-san is crazy fast!
H-He's so quick!
Point to Shindou!
1-0!
A low yo-yo!
Cut him off below!
I know!
This is but a mere glimpse of
the captain's explosiveness.
Even Grav-Shoes calibrated for a speeder can't
account for his extraordinary quickness.
No wonder he's the reigning champ.
So?
What next?
Just hurry up and take a
shortcut to the third line!
Roger!
Point to Shindou!
That makes it 2-0.
He's only getting started.
Hang in there, Misaki-senpai!
I'll get him this time!
Say, what do you make of this?
Shindou-san stopped?
If he'd shaken her off,
he could've taken the fourth buoy with ease.
He's kinda uncanny.
He's making fun of me, isn't he?
Don't fall for his provocation, Misaki.
I gotta say,
I hate people like him.
Calm down!
Don't take the bait!
I could use my speed to
keep racking up points,
but that wouldn't help you
practice, now would it?
So what are you getting at?
I'll throw you a bone and
take you on in a dogfight.
"Throw me a bone," you say?
Throw you a bone, yes.
Misaki.
Stay calm and take the bait.
Huh? You told me not to earlier.
I'm telling you to let your
body rage with a cool head.
Uh, I'm not sure I follow.
But the bottom line is I can zipzap
with him in a dogfight, right?
That's right.
Done with your little conference?
Yeah.
This what you mean by a
raging body and cool head?
Something like that.
Now fly around and zipzap
to your heart's content.
Roger that!
You've got some rather
amusing attacking maneuvers.
Gee, thanks!
That's one point, for starters!
And this makes it...
two!
Point to Shindou!
He scored twice!
Go wild, Misaki!
I don't care what you do!
Swing your arms, legs, and body around!
Easy for mew to say!
How will you attack me this time?
It's as if he sees through all her moves.
He's the reigning national champion.
He knows all there is to know about
FC theory and its basic moves.
Still, his reflexes are crazy.
I don't really get it,
but I do know they're both awesome!
Not coming at me?
I wish I could wipe that smile off your face!
Then why don't you take this more seriously?
You're a fighter, and yet you're
letting an all-rounder toy with you.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Misaki, focus on defense!
Don't wanna. I'm gonna attack.
No!
Don't wanna!
Oh, come on.
Misaki-senpai, an udon buffet!
All you can eat!
H-How about that?
Listen to me, and I'll feed you plenty!
Fine, I'll listen to you.
All right!
Yay!
Listen up, Misaki.
Ignore any chance you see to attack.
Shindou-san's just luring you in.
Just stick to him, and
keep dodging his attacks.
What's your plan, Hinata?
In a dogfight, Shindou-san
doesn't make the first move.
He's looking to land counters?
Yes.
I think that's our best shot.
You should attack me, Shindou-san.
Are you too scared?
Am I, now?!
She dodged it!
Stick close!
I know!
You're awfully persistent.
That I am!
Amazing. She's not faltering in
the least against Shindou.
She's sticking to him like glue!
Not half-bad, I say.
Tobisawa-san's awesome!
Not gonna take no for an answer, eh?
No, I won't!
Gotcha!
Damn, I attacked!
No udon?!
Yes, udon!
She did it!
Way to go, Misaki-senpai!
N-No way...
She scored against the captain?!
This match is over!
Shindou wins 4-1!
Thank you so much!
Thank you, too. That was more
productive than I expected.
Do you really think so?
H-Hey...
Of course.
Sorry about my provocative
style of play today.
I'd like to see more of your skills.
Let's save that for the summer tournament.
Hinata-kun.
Yes?
I'm looking forward to seeing
all of you get better.
Hey, you'll get hurt flying asleep!
Jeez.
Oh, right, Hinata-kun.
Ichinose-san said she wasn't mad
about the changing thing anymore.
Oh, that's a relief.
Misaki-senpai.
The training camp is over now,
so why don't we get some udon?
Oh, yeah! All-you-can-eat udon buffet!
But first...
Masaya!
Can we practice a bit now?
Now?
Just a bit.
Great.
Okay, Mashiro, Kurashina-san. Let's do this!
Seriously?
Hurry up!
All right! I'll join you!
You're not invited, Captain.
What are you saying?!
To Be Continued
Preview
Hurray! Hurray! Mashiro!
Hold it right there!
Meat makes me happy!
Episode Four:
"Meat Makes Me Happy!"